<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SUB MISI 1. Saifudin</string>

    <!--    club name-->
    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>English Premier League</item>
        <item>French Ligue 1</item>
        <item>German Bundesliga</item>
        <item>Italian Serie A</item>
        <item>Spanish La Liga</item>
        <item>American Mayor League</item>
        <item>Protugeuese Premiera Liga</item>
        <item>Australian A League</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--    club image-->
    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/english_premier_league</item>
        <item>@drawable/french_ligue_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/german_bundesliga</item>
        <item>@drawable/italian_serie_a</item>
        <item>@drawable/spanish_la_liga</item>
        <item>@drawable/american_mayor_league</item>
        <item>@drawable/portugeuese_premiera_liga</item>
        <item>@drawable/australian_a_league</item>
    </array>

    <!--    club desc-->
    <array name="club_desc">
        <item>The Premier League (often referred to as the English Premier League (EPL) outside England), is the top level of the English football league system. Contested by 20 clubs, it operates on a system of promotion and relegation with the English Football League (EFL).</item>
        <item>Ligue 1 (French pronunciation League 1, formerly known as Division 1), is the French professional league for association football clubs.</item>
        <item>The Fußball-Bundesliga (English: Football Federal League), commonly known as the Bundesliga, is a professional association football league in Germany and the football league with the highest average stadium attendance worldwide.</item>
        <item>Serie A, also called Serie A TIM due to sponsorship by Telecom Italia, is a professional league competition for football clubs located at the top of the Italian football league system and has been operating for over eighty years since the 1929–30 season.</item>
        <item>The Primera Division, commonly known as La Liga and as La Liga Santander for sponsorship reasons, is the top professional association football division of the Spanish football league system. </item>
        <item>Major League Soccer (MLS) is a professional soccer league representing the sport\'s highest level in both the United States and Canada. </item>
        <item>The Primeira Liga (First League Portuguese pronunciation: ), formerly called Primeira Division), is the top professional association football division of the Portuguese football league system.</item>
        <item>The A-League is a professional men\'s soccer league, run by Football Federation Australia (FFA). At the top of the Australian league system, it is the country\'s primary competition for the sport.</item>
    </array>
</resources>
